Guide to the Howard Gillette Papers, 1826-2018 MS0644.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Scholarly papers and publications, class materials and projects, 1826-2018; Series 4
  - Greater Washington Research Center: Greater Washington's Labor Shortage, 1988; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Greater Washington Research Center: Low-income Adults of Working Age in Washington, DC, 1988; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Greater Washington Research Center: Opportunity Ladders: Can Area Employment Possibilities Improve the Prospects for Washingtonians in Long-Term Poverty?, 1988; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - High Tech Careers: The Job Source for Engineering & Computer Professionals, 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - History Day News, 1995; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Housing Market Trends in Prince George's County, 1983; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Images of Brookland: The History and Architecture of a Washington Suburb, 1979; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Joint Committee, 1943-1958; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Lavender Vengeance and the Collective Heart Attack, 1996; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Managing the Nation's Capital, 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Montgomery County, Maryland: General Obligation Bonds, 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - National Capital Planning Commission, Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - New Dynamism in the Nation's Capital, Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Planning and Development Study for Marshall Height's Community Development Organization, 1981; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - A Plan to Preserve the Historic Resources of the Gettysburg Area, 1977; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Prince George's County Govt. Operations Review Commission, 1993; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Records of the Office of Public Buildings and Public Parks of the National Capital, 1992; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Robert Mills: Designs for Democracy, 1989; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Sites of Recollection, 1992; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - US Department of Agriculture: The Japanese Flowering Cherry Trees of Washington, DC, 1977; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - A Victim's Guide to the DC Criminal Justice System, 1993; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - AmCiv 50 (1991), 1990-1995; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Humanities 40, 1980-1989; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - AmCiv/Hist/PSU & RR 50, 1983-1995; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Justice & Beauty 1995, 1995-1997; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Seen Correspondence, 1995-1996; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Kids Discover Washington 1997, November 6, 1996; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Behind the Veil, 1996; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Southern City, National Ambition, 1995-1996; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - National Gallery of Art, 1991; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - National Building Museum Exhibit, 1997; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - DC Schools 1996, 1995-1996; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Urban Odyssey, 1986-1996; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Fauntory Papers, 1991-1992; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - DC Curriculum Project, 1994-1996; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Encyclopedia USA, 1991-1992; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Potomac River Basin Consortium, 1982-1984; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - DC Moments, March 11, 1991; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - DC Politics, June 10, 1996; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - GWU: Photos and Miscellaneous, 1999; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Back of the Big House, 1996; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Articles: By and about Howard Gillette Jr., 1994-2007; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Interview by Geoffrey Kabaservice, 2006; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Awards, 2006-2008; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Visionary Historian Award, 2018; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Programs, 1995-2009; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Book Reviews, 1973-2016; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Class Divide: Ads, Reviews, 2015-2016; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Camden After the Fall (UPA), 2004-2007; Series 4 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Justice and Beauty: University of Pennsylvania Press, 2006; Series 4 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Civitas by Design: Reviews/Critiques, 2010; Series 4 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Between Justice and Beauty: Reviews, 1995-1999 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Fair Housing Act at 50: Chancellor's Spring Research Symposium, 2018 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - 2017 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - URBS 104-401: The Transformation of Urban America, 2015-2018 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 2016 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, 2006-2015 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 2014-2015 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Mid-Atlantic, January 2015 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - DC Volume, 2014 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Price, Clement: Master Crafter of a Vital Public Square, 2015 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - 2013 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - 2012 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - 2010-2011 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Frederic M. Miller Memorial Lecture, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 2010-2011 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Camden Course, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Lubove, Roy, 1962-1996 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Bethlehem, Planning, 2006-2008 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - "After the Fall" Coverage, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Philadelphia: Constitution Center, Liberty Bell, 2003-2011 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - "Is this the Neoliberal Moment?", 2010 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - National Museum of Industrial History, Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - African American Mayors, 2001; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - The American Record: Images of the Nation's Past (Vol. II), 1982; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - American Quarterly (Vol. 25, No. 4), October 1973; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - American Quarterly (Vol. 35, No. 4), Fall 1983; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - American University Law Review Symposium (Vol. 48, No. 3), October 2, 1998; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Assessing James Rouse's Role in American City Planning, Spring 1999; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Award of Merit for "Washington Seen", September 12, 1996; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Award of Recognition Given by the New Jersey Historical Commission, Undated; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Center for Urban Research and Education Annual Report, 2012-2013; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Chicago History: The Magazine of the Chicago Historical Society, Winter 1989-1999; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Cincinnati Metropolitan Master Plan, 1948; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Citation for 25 Years of Valued Service at The George Washington University, 1995; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Columbian School of Arts and Sciences Celebration, May 17, 1997; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - The Community Builders Handbook, 1960; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Companion Encyclopedia of Geography (Vol. 1), 2007; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Composing Urban History and the Constitution of Civic Identities, 2003; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Crossing the Atlantic: Washington's Italian American Community, Winter 1997-1998; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Courier-Post: Book Propels Movement to Focus on City's Renewal, November 13, 2005; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Encyclopedia USA: District of Columbia (Vol. 21), April 1995; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - The Evolution of the Planned Shopping Center in Suburb and City, Autumn 1985; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - The Evolution of Washington's Italian American Community, 1996; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Farewell Lecture, May 5, 2011; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Film as Artifact, Undated; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - The George Washington University: Connections, Undated; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Harvard Design Magazine: Architecture, Landscape Architecture, Urban Design, and Planning, Spring/Summer 2006; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - The Inquirer: "Not the Bard of Camden, but the Scribe", May 3, 2011; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - The Johns Hopkins University Press, 1995; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Journal of American Ethnic History (Vol. 6, No. 1), Fall 1986; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Journal of the American Planning Association (Vol. 51, No. 4), Autumn 1985; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Journal of the American Planning Association (Vol. 65, No. 2), Spring 1999; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Journal of American Planning Association (Vol. 68, No. 2), Spring 2002; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Journal of Urban History (Vol. 9, No. 4), August 1983; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Journal of Urban History (Vol. 33, No. 2), January 2007; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Kenneth Jackson Award for Best Book (North American) in Urban History, 2006; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Magazine of History: Urban History (Vol. 5, No. 2), Fall 1990; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Manufactured Places, Undated; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - National Building Museum: Blueprints (Vol. 7, No. 4), Fall 1989; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - New Jersey Author's Award (Non-fiction, scholarly), 2006; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - The Ninth National Conference on American Planning History, November 2001; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Organization of American Historian Annual Meeting Convention Supplement, 1995; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania History: A Journal of Mid-Atlantic Studies (Vol. 68, No. 3), Summer 2001; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania History: A Journal of Mid-Atlantic Studies (Vol. 82, No. 3), Summer 2015; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - The Pennsylvania Magazine of History and Biography (Vol. 97, No. 2), April 1973; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Perspectives (Vol. 36, No. 9), December 1998; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Philadelphia's City Hall: Monument to a New Political Machine, April 1973; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Planning Perspectives (Vol. 18, No. 4), October 2003; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Planning Perspectives (Vol. 19, No. 3), July 2004; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Professor Emeritus Appointment, Rutgers University, November 2011; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - The Public Historian (Vol. 7, No. 1), Winter 1985; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Race Relations in Washington, DC, 1878-1955: A Photographic Essay, 1994; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Radio Times: "New Jersey Corruption", April 2, 2007; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Reviews in American History (Vol. 25, No. 3), September 1997; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Reviews in American History (Vol. 25, No. 4), December 1997; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Ripon Quarterly (Vol. 1, No. 1), Summer 1974; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Ripon Quarterly (Vol. 1, No. 2), Fall 1974; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Robert W. Kenny Prize for Innovation in Introductory Teaching, May 17, 1997; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - The Rutgers College Class of 1962 Presidential Public Service Award, May 4, 2006; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Social Science History (Vol. 14, No. 2), Summer 1990; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Southern City, National Ambition: The Growth of Early Washington, D.C., 1800-1860, 1995; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Strategic Government: Nixon's First Term, Undated; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Teaching the 1930s: A Cultural Approach, April 1974; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - UMGA TV: Book Chat, Camden After the Fall, December 7, 2005; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Urban America: Documenting the Planners, 1985; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Urban Morphology (Vol. 16, No. 1), 2012; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - The Wages of Disinvestment, Undated; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - The Walt Whitman Preservation President's Award for Distinguished Service, May 2, 2006; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - War and Memory: In the Aftermath of Vietnam, Undated; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Washingtonian, September 1995; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Washington City Paper: Jenkins on Historian Howard Gillette Jr., November 24, 1995; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Washington's Italian Community Exhibition, 1984; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - The Washington Post Magazine, October 29, 1995; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Civitas by Design, 1943-2009; Series 5
  This series contains materials related to Civitas by Design: Building Better Communities, from the Garden State to the New Urbanism. Contents include the book proposal and various research materials, such as scholarly publications, newspaper and magazine clippings, and notes. The materials range in date from 1943 to 2009.
  - Civitas by Design, 1959-2006; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Birch and Gardner: Review of Philanthropic Housing, 1981; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - The Regional Planning Association of America, 1995; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Silver, Christopher: "Neighborhood Planning in Historical Perspective", 1985-1986; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Katyal, Neal Kumar: "Architecture as Crime Control", 2002; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - New Urbanism, 1999-2007 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Public Housing Design, 1975-2007; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Baltimore: Frances Morton Froelichner, 1957-1979; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - New Urbanism: Inner City, 2000-2002; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Schuyler, David: "The New Urbanism and the Modern Metropolis", 1997-2002; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Disney Celebration, Florida, 1996-1999; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Prairie Crossing, 1998-2000; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Seaside, 1997; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Talen, Emily: New Urbanism, 2003-2009; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Kentlands, Maryland, 1988-1998; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Rouse, James, 1943-1998; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Rouse, James, 1954-1998; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Sandtown-Winchester, Baltimore, 1993-1997; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Land Forum O7, 1999; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Inner Harbor, Baltimore, 1979-2000; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Action, 1960; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Class Divide: Yale '64 and the Conflicted Legacy of the Sixties, 1955-2017; Series 6
  Boxes 21, 22, and 23 (folders 1-32) follow the materials' original order. Boxes 23 (folders 33-38), 24, 25 are arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains materials related to Class Divide: Yale '64 and the Conflicted Legacy of the Sixties. Contents within boxes 21, 22, and 23 (folders 1-32) include interviews, newspaper and magazine clippings, pamphlets, and correspondence. Contents within boxes 23 (folders 33-38), 24, 25, and 26 include publications written by Yale '64 students. The materials range in date from 1955 to 2017.
  - Arens, Edward, 2008; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Ashcroft, John, 2001-2010; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Armor, John, 1955-2018; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Bachmeyer, Tim, Undated; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Ball, Robert, 2010; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Basler, Frank, 2011; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Berk, Richard, 2011; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Bingham, Steve, 1968-2013; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Boardman, John, 2005-2012; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Bowe, William, 2011; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Bradford, Peter, 1978-2012; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Breen, Timothy, 2004-2013; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Carder, Brooks, 2001-2012; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Brunner, Ronald, 1982-2010; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Buell, Frederick, 2012-2013; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Byers, Russell, 1983-1999; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Cates, Ward, 2004-2016; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Caviness, Patrick, 1957-2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Cirie, Jack, 1965-2009; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Culliney, John, 1999; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Danforth, Nicholas, 1999-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Deford, Thomas McAdams (Mac), 2001-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Deloria, Philip Sam, 2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Donnelley, Strachan, 1998-2009; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Duesing, Bill, 2014; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Driver, Bruce, 2011-2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Duderstadt, James (Jim), 2000-2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Ferguson, Shannon, 1966-2010; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Freeman, Chas, 2007-2016; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Greenbladt, Stephen, 1994-2016; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Kaiser, Robert, 1967-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Huffman, Keith, 2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Kapica, Daniel (Dan), 1965-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Jeavon, John, 2002; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Shermon, Kent, 2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Lavely, Tony, 2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Lea, Sydney, 2011-2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Lee, Tony, 2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Liberman, Joseph (Joe), 1995-2013; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Lovejoy, Thomas, 1983-2017; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - MacBeth, Angus, 2008-2017; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - MacDonald, Angus, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - McKleroy, Alexander (Sandy), 2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - McBride, Jonathan (Jon), 2000-2010; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Musil, Robert K., 2010; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Nielson, Vigo (Chip), 1963-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Plimpton, David, 2007-2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Reynolds, Bradford, 1981-2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Rich, Joseph, 1969-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Roderick, Tom, 2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Rogers, James, 2007-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Roth, Williams, 1976-2015; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Schaffer, Christopher, 1992-2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Sherwood, Michael, 1988-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Sigal, Leon, 1998-2010; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Speth, James Gustave, 2004-2014; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Steiger, Paul, 2007-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Winter, Wallace, 2010-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Walton, Williams, 2001-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Berman, Daniel, 2013-2014; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - DuMont, Peaslee, 2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Harding, Pete, 2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Hilgendorf, Bob, 2005-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Huggins, Thomas Jackson (Jack), 2000-2013; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Klingelhofer, Stephan, 1990-2009; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Lamson, Robert, 2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Miner, James, 2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Morkriski, Charles, 2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - O'Donnell, Owen, 2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Pickett, George Edward Jr. (Chip), Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Price, Michael, 1995-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Powers, Thomas, 1994-2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Ranney, Edward, 1984-2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Reagin, Arthur, 2010-2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Schoenbrod, David, 2010; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Van Dyke, Jon, 2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Wishcamper, Lydell Joe, 2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Yale '64 List of Interviews, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Class Divide, 2010-2015; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - '64 Comments, 2014-2016; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Class Divide Events, 2015; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Yale '64 Reunion, 2004-2014; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Yale Daily News, 1960-1964; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Photos, 2002-2005; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Obituaries, 1999-2016; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Yale '64 Family, 2011-2012; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Yale-related Articles, 1960-2015; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Yale Admissions, 1962-2014; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Yale: African Americans, 2011; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - 1960s, 1968-2014; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Obituaries: 60s Figures, 1988-2015; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Generations, 1999-2015; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Baby Boomers, 2008-2012; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Esalen, 1999-2012; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Mad Men, 2009-2015; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Nixon, 2011; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - 1970s, 1970-2014; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Civil Rights, 1964-2013; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Fisher v. University of Texas: Affirmative-Action Ruling puts Colleges in Limbo, 2013; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Carmichael, Stokely, 1998-2014; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Thernstrom and Thernstrom, 1987-1998; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - The Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee, 1990-1989; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Policy, 1981-2014; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Middle East, 2006-2017; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Religion, 2004-2012; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Vietnam/War, 1969-2015; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Environment, 1997-2015; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Keystone XL, 2011-2014; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - CIA/FBI, 2005-2015; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - 9/11, Torture, Civil Liberties, 2001-2013; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Sexuality and the Family, 1998-2015; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Petchesky, Rosalind: "Antiabortion, Antifeminism, and the Rise of the New Right", 1981; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Coffin, William Sloan Jr., 1961-2006; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Lowenstein, Allard, 1994; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Lynd, Staughton, 1983; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Reich, Charles, 1970; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - G.B. Trudeau: " A Doonesbury Retrospective", November 25, 2010; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Yale Daily News: Course Critique, 1962; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Yale, 1962; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Prospectus for Class Divide: Social Change and Yale's Class of 1964, Undated; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Interview with Chas W. Freeman Jr., 1995; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - America's Owners Manual, 2009; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Armor, John: The Six O'Clock Man, 1988; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Ashcroft, John: Lessons from a Father to His Son, 1998; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Ashcroft, John: On My Honor, 1998; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Ashcroft, John: Securing America, 2006; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Bachmeyer and Everett: Disciplines in Transformation, 1979; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Breen, T.H.: The Revolution of the People, 2010; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Deford, Thomas McAdams: Eight Lost Years, 2009; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Duderstadt, James: For the Love of Michigan, 2014; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Duderstadt, James: A Master Plan for Higher Education in the Midwest, 2011; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Duderstadt, James: The Third Century, a Roadmap to the University of Michigan's Future, 2014; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Duderstadt, James: The View from the Helm, 1997; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Duesing, Bill: Living on Earth, 1993; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Field, John W.: Rendezvous with History, a History of the Yale Class of 1937 and its Times, 1984; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Freeman, Chas W. Jr.: America's Misadventures in the Middle East, 2010; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Greenbladt, Stephen: The Swerve, How the World Became Modern, 2011; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Owen: Stover at Yale, 1997; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Kaiser, Robert G.: Act of Congress, 2013; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Kapica, Daniel: Mangrove Seed Chronicles, 2007; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Kapica, Daniel: The Way of the Mangrove Seed, 2010; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Lea, Sydney: A Place in Mind, 1989; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 15)